coinimp.com 2019-03-11

# Privacy Policy | CoinIMP

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service, It also shows you options you have to control our use of that data. Headings are inserted for the convenience of the service only and are not to be considered when interpreting this document. Words in the singular mean and include the plural and vice versa. Words in the masculine mean and include the feminine and vice versa. 

CoinIMP may be referred hereinafter as we, or us, or the platform and operates the https://www.coinimp.com/ website which may be referred to hereinafter as also CoinIMP or The Service. 

Your use of our Services is governed by our Terms and Conditions, which contains exclusions of warranties and liability, and an applicable law clause as well. By using our service you are accepting this **Privacy Policy** and our Terms and Conditions. 

## Information Collection and Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

## What Data Do We Collect?

We may ask you to provide certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to the **email address** , which is asked at the moment of signing up.

## Usage Data

We may also collect information of how the Service is accessed and used. This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data and any other information necessary to track site traffic.

## Tracking & Cookies Data

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device (the directory where your browser is stored). Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can also remove the cookies on your browser. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. Examples of Cookies we use:

  * Session Cookies: we store Session Cookies when a visitor opens and navigates through our website and these cookies are usually removed at the user leaves the site.
  * Persistent Cookies: we use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings. These cookies are not
  * Secure Cookies: we use this setting to guarantee that the cookie is returned to the application over encrypted connections.

## How to Disable or Clear Cookies on your Browser?

## Use of Data

CoinIMP uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and optimize the site and the service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer care and support
  * To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
  * To monitor the usage of the Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To measure our audience

## Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those in your jurisdiction.

We are an advertisement platform where website managers can host impressions (the times a visitor sees an ad on a website) in the form of tokens and then use those tokens (saved impressions) on exchanges or as payment method. If you choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to every place our servers operate and process it there.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this **Privacy Policy** and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure of Data

CoinIMP may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * Comply with a legal obligation.
  * Protect and defend our/your rights.
  * Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service.
  * Protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public.
  * Protect against legal liability.

## Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the **Privacy Policy** of every site you visit.

We have no control over and hold no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address participants who have not attained the legal age of their country of residence. They must be legally able, which means full legal standing on their own behalf.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under their legal age. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us with the proofs to support your claim. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children, we usually take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our **Privacy Policy** from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new **Privacy Policy** on this page. We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our site, prior to the change becoming effective on the "effective date" mentioned at the top of this **Privacy Policy**.

You are advised to review this **Privacy Policy** periodically for any changes. Changes to this **Privacy Policy** are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this **Privacy Policy** , please use the following email to contact us: [support@coinimp.com](mailto:support@coinimp.com)
